1. 1. Hi, my name is Andy.
一，听句子，根据所听到的内容选择正确答语。
每小题念两遍。
听完每句话后，你都有五秒钟的时间来回答有关小。
题和阅读下一小题。
2. Have a good holiday.
3. Don't fight with your classmates,
4. Mom, could I go out for dinner with my friends?
5. I think college students should be allowed to have part -time jobs.
2. 6. The children are planting trees.
二，听句子，选择与所听句子内容相符的图片。
每小题念两遍。
听前，你将有五秒钟的读图时间。
听完后，每小题将给出五秒钟的作答。
7. Peter underlined the words he heard.
8. Lily is helping an old lady cross the street.
9. Mr. Young often exercises at 6.30 in the morning.
10. It's wonderful to see plays in this theatre.
3. 11. Lisa, what's your favorite subject?
听对".话。
根据对话内容及问题选择正确答案。
每小题念两遍。
听完每段对话后，你都有五秒钟的时间来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题。
Is it music or art?
12. favorite subject is history.
12. I can't find my keys.
I thought I left them in the bag.
Are they on the sofa or table?
14. here they are, on the sofa.
15. Where are the keys?
16. can't find my keys.
I thought I left them in the bag.
17. Are they on the sofa or table?
18. here they are, on the sofa.
19. Where are the keys?
I can't I What time is your piano lesson, 22.
It's at 8.45.
What about yours, 23.
Oh, well, mine starts half an hour later, a quarter past nine.
What time does Tom's piano lesson start?
25. time is your piano lesson,
26. It's at 8.45.
What about yours, Tom?
27. Oh, well, mine starts half an hour later, a quarter past nine.
Question. What time does Tom's piano lesson start?
14. Hi, Victor.
Let's see a movie after lunch.
I'd like to, but I've got a problem with my leg.
I will go to hospital this afternoon.
Question. What is Victor going to do this afternoon?
Hi, Victor. Let's see a movie after lunch.
I'd like to, but I've got a problem with my leg.
I will go to hospital this afternoon.
Question. What is Victor going to do this afternoon?
15. Have you finished?
Yes, thank you.
It's delicious. Okay.
Would you like anything else?
Can I bring the dessert menu?
No, thank you.
Question. What's the relationship between the two speakers?
Have you finished?
Yes, thank you.
It's delicious. Okay.
Would you like anything else?
Can I bring the dessert menu?
No, thank you.
What's the relationship between the two speakers?
16. Do you like swimming?
Yes, I do.
It's fun. What about you?
Well, it's good for health, but a little bit difficult.
I love playing tennis.
It's cool. Question.
What does the girl think of tennis?
Do you like swimming?
Yes, I do.
It's fun. What about you?
Well, it's good for health, but a little bit difficult.
I love playing tennis.
It's cool. Question.
What does the girl think of tennis?
Number 17. me.
Could you please tell me the way to the nearest subway station?
Sorry, I don't know, because I usually drive.
You can ask the policeman over there.
Thank you all the same.
Question. Where are the two speakers?
Excuse me. Could you please tell me the way to the nearest subway station?
Sorry, I don't know, because I usually drive.
You can ask the policeman over there.
Thank you all the same.
Question. Where are the two speakers?
Number 18. Look, it's snowing heavily.
It doesn't snow often in Wow, fantastic.
We can make a snowman.
Question. How does the girl feel?
Look, it's snowing heavily.
It doesn't snow often in Chengdu.
Wow, fantastic. We can make a snowman.
How does the girl feel?
Number 19. Have you ever read the poem
咏梅》
by the great leader
毛泽东？
No, I haven't.
Can you tell me something about it?
Sure, Yong praising something.
咏梅》
is a kind of flower.
In this poem, Yong Mei means praising heroes.
Oh, I see.
Question. What does Mei refer to in the poem?
Have you ever read the poem Yong Mei by the great leader
毛泽东.
No, I haven't.
Can you tell me something about it?
Sure, Yong can mean praising something.
is a kind of flower.
In this poem, Yong Mei means praising heroes.
Oh, I see.
Question. What does Mei refer to in the poem?
Number 20. Hey Ling, don't push yourself too hard.
You can't become an English expert just after a few lessons.
Oh, what should I do?
Take it easy.
Keep trying and your English will be improved.
Question. What does the woman want Ling to do?
Hey Ling, don't push yourself too hard.
You can't become an English expert just after a few lessons.
Oh, what should I do?
Take it easy.
Keep trying and your English will be improved.
Question. What does the woman want Ling to do?
Question. What to do?
四。
听短文，根据短文内容选择正确答案。
短文念两遍。
听前，你将有十五秒钟的读题时间。
听完后，每小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。
Good morning everyone.
It's always great to welcome new members to the Running Club.
I'm the coach, Daniel Black.
You will find my email address on our website.
The club gets together one evening every week on Tuesdays.
I post information about the runs on Sundays.
As it's summer, we're still meeting at 7 o 'clock.
However, that will change next month.
In the ultimate winter, we meet at 5.30.
We do two runs each week.
One is 12 kilometers and there is a shorter run for beginners and children.
That's 6 kilometers.
You can choose which run you want to do.
When the weather is good, we run through the forest.
But if it's wet, we run in the park.
We also have a special club day every year.
This year, that will be on June the 18th at Jacksonville.
Last year, we had a theme party at the house of a club member.
And this year, we're going to have a picnic.
So, does anyone have any questions?
Good morning everyone.
It's always great to welcome new members to the Running Club.
I'm the coach, Daniel Black.
You'll find my email address on our website.
The club gets together one evening every week on Tuesdays.
I post information about the runs on Sundays.
As it's summer, we're still meeting at 7 o
However, that will change next month.
In the autumn and we meet at 5.30.
We do two runs each week.
One is 12 kilometers, and there's a shorter run for beginners and children.
That's 6 kilometers.
You can choose which run you want to do.
When the weather is good, we run through the forest.
But if it's wet, we run in the park.
We also have a special club day every year.
This year, that will be on June the 18th at Jacksonville.
Last year, we had a theme party at the house of a club member.
And this year, we're going to have a picnic.
So, does anyone have any questions?
五，听短文，根据短文内容完成图。
表中所缺信息。
Read There are a lot of things you can do to make your high school experience one of
短文念三遍。
听前，你将有二十五秒钟的读题时间。
the best times of your life.
yourself be who you really are.
During high school, you may feel under pressure to fit in.
You need to try your best to find the unhappy feelings and learn to have a change.
High school actually gives you a chance to discover a real you and grow as a person.
But keep in mind, are the only one who can make the change.
friends with different kinds of Try to start a conversation with people, especially
strangers. Everybody has something helpful for your growth.
Over time, you'll develop a friend group filled with people that like you for who
you are. This can add a lot of value to your life.
Don't avoid communicating with your teachers.
Do your best to be kind and friendly to everybody that you take a class from.
If possible, spend a few minutes before or after class talking with your teachers
about things of their subject.
There are a lot of things you can do to make your high school experience one of the
best times of your life.
Let yourself be who you really are.
During high school, you may feel under pressure to fit in.
You need to try your best to find the unhappy feelings and learn to have a change.
school actually gives you a chance to discover a real you and grow as a person.
But keep in mind, you are the only one who can make the change.
Make friends with different kinds of people.
Try to start a conversation with people, especially strangers.
Everybody has something helpful for your growth.
Over time, you will develop a friend group filled with people that like you for who
you are. This can add a lot of value to your life.
Don't avoid communicating with your teachers.
Do your best to be kind and friendly to everybody that you take a class from.
If possible, spend a few minutes before or after class talking with your teachers
about things of their subject.
There are a lot of things you can do to make your high school experience one of the
best times of your life.
Let yourself be who you really are.
During high school, you may feel under pressure to fit in.
You need to try your best to find the unhappy feelings and learn to have a change.
High school actually gives you a chance to discover a real you and grow as a person.
But keep in mind, you are the only one who can make the change.
Make friends with different kinds of
Try to start a conversation with people, especially strangers.
Everybody has something helpful for your growth.
Over time, you will develop a friend group filled with people that like you for who
you are. This can add a lot of value to your life.
Don't avoid communicating with your teachers.
Do your best to be kind and friendly to everybody that you take a class from.
If possible, spend a few minutes before or after class talking with your teachers
about things of their subject.
听力测试结束，请关注“锦鲤英语”微信公众号
Thank you